<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on CheckBook.cash</title>
    <link>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on CheckBook.cash</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 14:52:47 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Checkbook Welcomes EVM Users</title>
      <link>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/checkbook-welcomes-evm-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 14:52:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/checkbook-welcomes-evm-users/</guid>
      <description>Checkbook.cash welcomes EVM users to try out smartBCH!
Checkbook.cash is an airdrop tool for smartBCH, a sidechain of Bitcoin Cash with EVM&amp;amp;Web3 compatibility. To incentive EVM users to add smartBCH network to their web3 wallet such as MetaMask, free tokens will be airdropped through checkbook.cash.
So the checkbook development team picked about 5 million active accounts of Ethereum and BSC, according to their transaction logs in the past six months. Each account will be airdropped with a $CATS check with about $5 value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Checks Through BCHCC Bridge</title>
      <link>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/get-checks-through-bchcc-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 09:42:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/get-checks-through-bchcc-bridge/</guid>
      <description>To test the new version of CheckBook DApp with generally-supported encrypted memos, we are giving out checks together with bchcc.cash, a BCH-to-smartBCH bridge.
The rule is simple: for each cross-chain transfer through bchcc.cash, a check with some $CATS will also be sent to the receiver of cross-chain BCH. The rule does not take the status of the receiver into account. And the count is not limited: a receiver can get multiple checks if she transferred BCH through BCHCC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Checks through Wagon.cash Bridge</title>
      <link>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/get-checks-through-wagoncash-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 01:05:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/get-checks-through-wagoncash-bridge/</guid>
      <description>To test the new version of CheckBook DApp, we are giving out checks together with wagon.cash, a BCH-to-smartBCH bridge.
The rule is simple: for each cross-chain transfer through wagon.cash, a check with some $CATS will also be sent to the receiver of cross-chain BCH. The rule does not take the transfer amount or the status of the receiver into account. And the count is not limited: a receiver can get multiple checks if she transferred BCH through wagon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other Usages of Blockchain Cheques</title>
      <link>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/other-usages-of-blockchain-cheques/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 07:45:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/other-usages-of-blockchain-cheques/</guid>
      <description>Besides airdropping, blockchain cheques can be useful in several other scenarios. It is not the best solution for these scenarios, but it can be good enough. Here we introduce some of such scenarios. For each one of them, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to develop a dedicated DApp which does a better job than blockchain cheque. However, each DApp needs time and human resource to develop, and time to gain trust of its users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world from blockchain cheques</title>
      <link>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/hello-world-from-blockchain-cheques/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 08:45:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.checkbook.cash/posts/hello-world-from-blockchain-cheques/</guid>
      <description>We are the developers of smartBCH side chain. Although our main mission is to develop the full-node client of smartBCH, we also would like to contribute some useful utilities to its ecosystem. So we created the DApp for blockchain cheques and this site.
Why do we design such a DApp? Because we believe some features of paper checks can be borrowed to enrich the methods for airdropping. First of all, it is a Notification Center of airdrops.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
